zoovy.com 2012-10-22

# Zoovy Privacy Policy

## 1\. PRIVACY STATEMENT

Zoovy, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website zoovy.com. This policy does not address the individual websites that may be hosted by Zoovy. Zoovy recommends, but does not require that these individual sites poses an individual privacy statement. You should contact the owner of the individual site, regarding their privacy policy and information disclosure practices. 

#### 2\. GATHERING OF SYSTEM INFORMATION

We use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to broad demographic information, and to establish a historical security pattern to detect unauthorized access to your account. 

#### 3\. TRACKING OF COOKIES

A "cookie" is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. We use cookies to help us provide personal services and to allow you to sign-in to our site without having to enter your name and password each time. Our site uses cookies to keep track of logins, and shopping carts, we may also periodically use cookies as a placeholder for a specific method or process in our system. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to enter your password on every page. We track how often you are given cookies, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to determine if authorized access has been granted. Furthermore we also allow our partners to use cookies to make sure you don't see the same dadvertisement repeatedly. 

#### 4\. CUSTOMER IDENTIFABLE INFORMATION 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us in depth contact information, this information is used to help us serve you better, it is not shared with third parties, except when you specifically authorize us. See section (5) below. Furthermore our site requires many unique identifiers such as social security number, federal tax identification, and financial information such as bank accounts and credit cards. This information is strictly between you and us; we do not share this information with our partners, unless you explicitly authorize us to. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor, by our staff when necessary. The majority of our system is based on opt-in lists, which provide users the ability to opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers are used for internal verification to verify the user's identity, and in some cases are used when reporting to government agencies for purposes required by law. 

#### 5\. FOREIGN SYSTEMS

This site contains links to other, non Zoovy Partner sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Zoovy will only transmit your information to Zoovy partners when you have elected to sign up for a co-branded service that is linked with the Zoovy system. For your convenience we will then transmit only the information required by the partner, through a secure channel to avoid you needing to re-enter the information. However it is your responsibility to ensure that you agree to the third parties privacy policy, and relevant licensing statements prior to authorizing us to transmit your information. For your convenience a link may be provided allowing you to review any privacy policies and licensing statements prior to data transmission. 

#### 6\. INTERNAL USE OF INFORMATION

Our site provides a mechanism for people to send feedback and request more information. This information is not uniquely stored, but may be aggregated with other data to insure that we properly meet customers' expectations and have the necessary resources planned to accommodate future growth. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services. Features of our site provide a form for customers to request information about products, and services from other vendors. Contact information from the order form is handed to the responsible organization; you should contact the organization that is listed on the form to ensure their privacy policy is acceptable to you. 

#### 7\. CONTESTS AND SURVEYS

From time to time we may have optional online surveys in conjunction with; or exclusive of contests. These forms will ask visitors for contact information such as email address and broad demographic information including but not limited to zip code, age, or income level. We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

#### 8\. PUBLIC INFORMATION

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### 9\. SECURITY

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. This site uses a combination of firewalls, packet filters, security patches, monitoring software, and advanced cryptographic software in conjunction with secure sockets layer to ensure you personal data is secure from unauthorized access. Unless you explicitly request that we do not use advanced security, by default advanced security will always be on. Only certain employees have access to the information you provide us. For example, we impose strict rules on our employees who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. 

#### 10\. DATA SHARING PRACTICES

As part of the service we provide we routinely collect and store information from customers who buy from a user of our service. Any data which is collected and stored on our servers along with sales data, product information, is property of the user - with the following exceptions: 

We routinely inspect the data to verify integrity of the information.   
We share information about customers with an ISP provided the ISP has demonstrated they have a pre-existing relationship.   
We share information about customers with a marketplace provided the marketplace has demonstrated they already have a pre-existing relationship with the customer.   
We routinely compile aggregate sales statistics information.

#### 11\. CHOICE OPT-OUT

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

You can send email to [info@zoovy.com](mailto:info@zoovy.com)

You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Zoovy, Inc.  
5868 Owens Ave.  
Suite #150  
Carlsbad, CA. 92008  
  
You can call the following telephone number:  760-944-7660  
877-ZOOVY4U (toll free)  
You may send us a facsimile at 425-699-7859 

#### 12\. COPYRIGHT POLICY

Copyright. Without limiting any other remedies, Zoovy may suspend or terminate your account if you are found to be infringing upon the copyright, trademark or other rights of third parties. Copyright, or Trademark owners can report infringing items, and have such items removed. Once the identity of a copyright or trademark owner is established, the owners may have limited access to some of your personally identifiable information as described in the Zoovy Privacy Policy. 

#### 13\. UPDATE POLICY

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Customers of a user may do this by going to the users respective website. Zoovy users may do this by visiting http://www.zoovy.com/ and supplying a system assigned username and password. 

#### 14\. CONTACTING ZOOVY

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [click here](http://www.zoovy.com/company/contact) or contact:

Zoovy, Inc.  
Customer Care  
5868 Owens Ave.  
Suite #150  
Carlsbad, CA. 92008  

|
